Olasubomi Archibong

A creative designer with extensive experience in graphic and visual design dedicated to improving the human experience through a user-centric approach to design. A strong advocate for the design thinking process and committed to being a reliable and collaborative team player.

Education

University of Lagos - Nigeria

Soft Skills

Empathy

Creativity

Communication

Active Listening

Collaboration

Class of 2014 B.Sc Architecture

CareerFoundry - Online

Dec 2022 - Present UX Design Immersion

Skills & Tools

ToolsPhotoshop
Illustrator

Illustrator
Premiere Pro
After Effects

Figma WordPress HTML/CSS JavaScript

Design Skills

Branding & Identity
Web Design
Design Thinking
Wireframing & Prototyping
Information Architecture
Visual Design

Projects

<u>Sitipay.com</u> — A financial solution for students April 2023 - Present

- Recognized the need for educating university students about financial topics to equip them for the real world.
- Conducted comprehensive competitive analyses and user interviews to shape personas and user flows, providing valuable insights throughout the design thinking process.
- Developed a responsive web app that serves as a multifunctional platform, combining financial learning, savings, and investment features.

Experience

Webmaster — Sonova

May 2020 - Present

- Update and manage websites for Sonova's Brands (Phonak, Unitron, Hansaton) to align with global and local campaign objectives, enhancing user experience and driving engagement.
- Ensure project success by conducting scoping sessions, maintaining team KANBAN, and delivering results that exceeded stakeholder expectations.
- Led the successful creation and launch of Sonova's Brand websites across multiple countries and languages - increasing brand visibility and customer engagement.
- Scheduled daily social posts, created insightful reports, and provided valuable feedback to enhance the online presence of Sonova's Brands - fostering engagement and driving strategic growth.

Founder - Colorteam.io

July 2017 - Present

- Identified the need for affordable digital marketing solutions within the startup community, leading to the founding of Colorteam in 2017. Services offered include but not limited to branding, websites, social media management, video editing, and presentation design.
- Successfully served over 100 clients worldwide, including Fortune 500 companies, by providing stateof-the-art digital marketing solutions. Our contributions to their brands have been highly acclaimed.

